♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Odd, how you doing?
Shield!
I’m just about through with Norbert!
Odd, don’t tell me you’re still giving them stupid names.
Do you have any idea what kind of attack it is, Jeremie?
No, but with a bit of luck, we’re onto it faster than Xana anticipated.
That’s right, when Odd checks in, Xana checks out!
Hey, that’s not fair guys!
What’s wrong?
I don’t know. I can’t move.
I’m coming.
Super sprint!
Jeremie, we’ve got a problem.
I see it, but I can’t figure it out.
Norbert, you’re not gonna…
Oh no. Aelita, I’ll try to distract them away from you.
The Krab is bugged too! Go for it!
Great job, Aelita. Nice one.
That was so weird. As if everything bugged up.
I don’t know what could have happened. Of course, that might have been Xana’s attack.
What, that’s all you can come up with?
Hey, you know, you better start working on your A-game.
I suppose that was your A-game against your pal Norbert.
I’ve got some routine checks to carry out,
just to be sure it was Xana’s attack.
Go on and eat without me, I’ll catch up.
Can I have your portion?
Mh hm
Fantastic!
Shepherd's Pie tonight!
Yeah, and it’s also boys’ dorm inspection, so don’t be too long Jeremie.
This’ll take a few minutes, that’s all.
No, Kwi, tonight you stay here.
The last thing we need is for Jim to find you.
My little diggity dog.
Now then, let me remind you that your rooms should be impeccable order.
Keeping your room neat and clean is a cen-i-qua- uh,
siney-quat uh what do you call it? Cine-
-matogrophy?
Right! No, that’s not it. Anyway, it’s an important part of a good night’s sleep.
He who sleeps well, lives well.
And that’s why man wasn’t meant to live in a garbage dump!
‘Cause you can’t sleep well.
Wait a minute. Hey, where’s Belpois!?
Uh, in the bathroom, Jim.
What? You mean all this time?
Shepherd's Pie doesn’t agree with him.
Mh hm
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
What’s all this stuff about?
Uh oh, it’s getting weirder.
But, I don’t believe it! This is sabotage! Somebody’s been in here.
Oh no!
Sabotage?
Yes, by Michael Reilly, possessed by Xana.
That’s what yesterday’s attack was.
And the bugs that prevented you from fighting were caused--
--by the drop in calculating capacity of the Super Computer.
What a mess, think you can fix it?
Yes, but I’ve got to do it fast or else we’re gonna be in big trouble guys.
We are, how come?
It’s simple, the internal circuit has been badly damaged.
Right now, the quantum bytes are collapsing one after the other.
The dropping computing speed will become more and more serious, right up until-
Stop, reader’s digest version, how much time do we have?
Three hours.
Are you absolutely sure that the whole thing will be destroyed?
Definitely. It’s already lost a lot of speed.
I even tried to launch a return to the past to see - no way.
I gotta pick some stuff from my room, then I’m gonna head back over.
As for your classes, you’ll have to think of some phony excuses.
Sorry guys, but I gotta go now.
Chardin is taking us to see an exhibit, keep be posted, huh?
Okay.
Belpois! Belpois!
Oh no. The inspection.
Did you have time to clean your room?
You mean, since last week? No way.
I looked for you everywhere last night.
Yours is the only room I haven’t inspected.
Get up, come on, on your feet, now!
So, you can’t eat Shepherd’s Pie either, huh?
What’s he talking about?
Nevermind.
Huh?
What on earth do you call this, Belpois?
Uh, it’s called my room.
An excellent student like you?
You ought to be ashamed.
You are not leaving this room until you make it one hundred percent spick and span,
do you understand?
And those things, what are they?
Uh, computer magazines.
Our Einstein really is a geek, isn’t he?
Hey, what do you think you three are doing here?
Well, we thought he might be able to use some help.
He’s gonna do it himself without anyone’s help.
Go to your classes right now and double time!
There’s no way Jim’s gonna get off Jeremie’s back until he’s through cleaning up.
Yeah, and it three hours, it’s adios Supercomputer.
Maybe I can try to fix it.
Actually, I bet that’s what Jeremie meant when he gave me this box.
Do you think you can do it?
At least I can try to limit the damage.
Besides, we don’t have much of a choice.
Mh mh.
Go to class and tell them I got sick from…
uh… the Shepherd’s Pie.
I’ll let you know if I come up with anything.
Okay.
I’m off.
Good luck, Princess.
Thanks.
Sir, uh, the bus is late. When’s it gonna come?
There isn’t any. We are going to walk. Anything for art!
(AIRPLANE NOISES)
JIM: Straighten her out. You’re gonna hover in! Can’t you see you got an F4 Phantom on your tail?
Jim?
Hm, ah, yeah, what? What do you want?
We heard that one of the students failed his dorm room inspection?
Could you tell us who that might be?
I certainly will not! When it comes to our students,
I refuse to divulge any names!
Especially when we’re talking about Jeremie Belpois.
Oh no, Xana is on the attack. Jim,
where are you? I finished.
Is it okay if I go now?
Oh no. An activated tower.
(PHONE RINGING)
Aelita? Yeah, okay, we’re on our way.
Activated tower. We’re going in. I’ll tell Yumi.
Breath deeply.
Nothing like taking in a breath of fresh air before taking in some fine art.
(PHONE RINGING)
What?
Which part of the museum are you gonna visit first, huh, William?
The impressionist, or the pop art?
Neither. The gift shop.
I’m gonna try and get something there for Yumi.
What would you like, Yumi? Y-
Huh, well as usual, she couldn’t wait to give me the slip.
Let’s get to work.
You think that Aelita got the thing fixed yet, huh, Ulrich?
We’ll find out soon enough-
Hey, what happened?
Hey!
Got any sunblock?
Alright, now get to class and hurry it up.
Thanks Jim. See ya!
(BOXES CLATTERING)
Belpois, get back in here right now!
Yes, Jeremie, I did what I could in the meantime
but I don’t know if it will hold up.
The others? No, nothing yet. Okay then, hurry up.
Odd, try to free my hand.
What are you joking?
First I’d love to be able to move my own.
There they are. Huh? Oh.
Pretty good timing.
Hey! Hang on.
Ah, watch it Einstein. Coordinations never been your thing.
Nice one.
Hey! Ulrich, run!
Join Aelita and try to deactivate the tower! Hurry!
Where are the others?
Jeremie and Odd are kinda tied up.
We’ll have to do without them.
Yumi isn’t here yet?
No.
(PHONE RINGING)
Ulrich. Same here, these stupid roots are blocking the way.
Oh no, don’t wait for me-
Yumi! No time to lose. Yumi’s in trouble, Aelita.
Okay, I’ll start up a self-virtualization program.
Did you manage to fix the Super Computer?
Well, just temporarily.
Here we go.
Come on.
How are we gonna get out of this one?
Just like we said.
But we didn’t say anything.
That’s why we have a problem.
Hold on, I think I may have an idea.
That’s great. I’m dying to hear it.
No time, but when I give you the signal,
you’ve got to try with all of your might to get yourself free, okay.
I should try to get free, huh?
I could have thought of that without your help.
You gotta trust me, Odd.
Can’t you think of something more convincing to say for once?
Okay, two Tarantulas, not exactly the end of the world.
Should we use force?
Is there any other way?
Our brains.
Don’t have any.
Super sprint.
Oh no!
Since I’m in black and white, might as well fight the old fashioned way.
En garde! Touche!
This time, we’ve had it.
Oh no, not now!
Cool.
Hey, what happened?
Nothing special, the bugs also affect the monsters.
Well that kinda makes things even for once.
The signal?
Hold on.
Now!
Quick, let’s get out of here.
Get to the scanner room!
Yes sir!
How many life points do you think you have left?
Definitely less than you.
That’s right, so you’d better watch it.
Jeremie, you’re there, that’s cool.
Yeah, and Odd’s coming to the rescue.
Scanner, Odd.
Virtualization.
Triplicate.
Good job, Aelita.
Uh oh. Right. Any last words before we both get devirtualized?
Laser Arrow!
Well that’s what I wanted to hear. Good to see you, Odd!
Cootchie coo!
Huh, guess you’re not ticklish under the claws.
Here’s a little something to get around with.
Saddle up, princess.
Help! Anyone out there, help!
Sorry guys, the Super Computer is losing more and more power.
You’ll have to go on foot.
Jeremie, I didn’t have time to finish the repairs.
I know, Aelita, but you did a great job.
It’s okay, I can finish up.
Do it as fast as you can. It’s bugging up more and more.
And we still haven’t heard anything from Yumi!
I’ll do whatever I can.
You just worry about that stupid tower.
Here comes another mega problem.
There, that ought to do it.
Oh no, that is so uncool.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Ouch!
How you doing, Einstein? It’s killing us!
We can’t take a step without bugging up!
I’m almost there.
Okay, all I have to do is reboot the works.
Better step on it.
Oh no.
What?
I don’t have enough juice to reboot the Super Computer!
If we could only deactivate the tower,
I could use its energy to restart the whole system.
That’s fine, Jeremie, but over here,
we can’t deactivate the tower unless you reboot the system.
There is one way to do it.
Go on, I’m listening.
Destroy the Ice Sector.
Good old Aelita, even during the worst of times,
she keeps her sense of humor.
Uh, you mean you weren’t kidding?
Aelita, that’s crazy.
Jeremie, it’s the only way to recover some energy--
--and avoid total destruction of the Super Computer.
And if that happens, Lyoko disappears and us with it.
We don’t have a choice.
Besides, that would automatically deactivate the tower.
She’s right. Go on, do it Aelita.
When I restart the system, I won’t be able to rematerialize you.
You’ll have to manage on your own.
Got it.
Right, listen up. Aelita, you take care of Odd.
Odd, you zap me. On three. One-
Hold it. We zap each other on three,
or do we count to three and then zap each other?
You always pull this on me, Odd. No,
we zap each other on three, okay? One-
Wait!
Aelita, don’t miss, okay?
Odd!
Okay, okay.
One… two… three!
The activated tower’s disappeared!
Reboot system.
Alright!
Three?
Right, the repairs are only temporary,
but at least they’ll let us keep on fighting Xana.
We managed to save the Supercomputer.
You did great, Aelita. Sissi’s right to call you Mrs. Einstein.
Don’t forget that this last little adventure of ours cost us the Ice Sector.
Yeah, that is a shame. I’m gonna have to find a way--
--to virtualize you directly into Sector Five from now on.
It’s okay, don’t worry.
As long as the Mountain Sector stays together, there’s still hope.
Yeah, but for how long?
Hey! I didn’t know you had the solutions for Bug Fighter Attack.
You mind?
Be careful not to knock anything over.
Jim is coming back tomorrow morning to do another inspec-
(BOXES CLATTERING)
Sorry. Uh, you were saying?
Forget it.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS